RG 005:035, Office of the Governor: Thomas J. Meskill (1971-1975)
Connecticut State Library
- Series 14. Speeches, 1971-1974
  - Commerce Outlook, 1974 (Box A-905)
  - Committee to Reelect the President, 1972 January 25 (Box A-905)
  - Conference on the Arts, 1972 September 14 (Box A-905)
  - Connecticut Association of Municipal Attorneys, 1972 October 15 (Box A-905)
  - Connecticut Association of Street and Highway Officials, 1973 April 11 (Box A-905)
  - Connecticut Association of Tax Assessors, 1973 November 29 (Box A-905)
  - Connecticut Chamber of Commerce, 1974 February 14 (Box A-905)
  - Connecticut Child Welfare Association Legislative Day, 1973 January 29 (Box A-905)
  - Connecticut Child Welfare Association Legislative Day, 1973 September 10 (Box A-905)
  - Connecticut Child Welfare Association Legislative Day, 1974 January 28 (Box A-905)
  - Connecticut Credit Union League, 1973 May 4 (Box A-905)
  - Connecticut Federation of Student Councils, 1971 August 8 (Box A-905)
  - Connecticut Public Expenditure Council, 1974 May 22 (Box A-905)
  - Connecticut Public Expenditure Council, 1973 May 17 (Box A-905)
  - Connecticut State Employee Convention, 1972 October 7 (Box A-905)
  - Connecticut State Plumbers Association, 1973 May 21 (Box A-905)
  - Connecticut Student Loan Foundation, 1973 April 19 (Box A-905)
  - Connecticut Tax Collectors Association, 1973 May 17 (Box A-905)
  - Corrections (Box A-905)
  - Credibility of Government (Box A-905)
  - Crime Prevention, 1972 February 3 (Box A-905)
  - Cromwell Bridge, 1973 May 18 (Box A-905)
  - Danbury Regional Center, 1973 March 29 (Box A-905)
  - Danbury Rotary, 1971 October 6 (Box A-905)
  - Danbury Rotary, 1972 October 4 (Box A-905)
  - Day Care Nutrition Symposium, 1973 October 16 (Box A-905)
  - Dedication of Mental Health Center, 1973 May 21 (Box A-905)
  - Derby-Shelton Kiwanis and Rotary Club, 1973 March 20 (Box A-905)
  - Development Commission, 1971 July 16 (Box A-905)
  - Drug Insert (Box A-905)
  - Drugs, 1971 October 5 (Box A-905)
  - Drugs, 1972 November 9 (Box A-905)
  - Drunken Driving, 1972 March 10 (Box A-905)
  - Drunken Driving, 1972 November 19 (Box A-905)
  - Eastern Star, 1972 April 28 (Box A-906)
  - Eastern States Exposition, 1972 September 20 (Box A-906)
  - Economic Development, 1973 April 6 (Box A-906)
  - Education, 1972 September 20 (Box A-906)
  - Elderly (Box A-906)
  - Electric Boat Management, 1972 February 9 (Box A-906)
  - Employee Bonus, 1973 May 30 (Box A-906)
  - Employee: Handicapped, 1973 April 19 (Box A-906)
  - Employee Suggestions, 1973 April 5 (Box A-906)
  - Energy Crisis, 1973 November 2 (Box A-906)
  - Energy Luncheon, 1974 May 31 (Box A-906)
  - Energy Policy Speech, 1973 June 5 (Box A-906)
  - Energy Public Hearing, 1974 November 11 (Box A-906)
  - Energy Speech, 1974 March 3 (Box A-906)
  - Energy Speech to Mayors, 1973 November 26 (Box A-906)
  - Enfield Chamber of Commerce, 1973 April 25 (Box A-906)
  - Environment Committee Symposium, 1973 November 30 (Box A-906)
  - Environment Speeches (Box A-906)
  - Erosion and Sedimentation Conference, 1973 May 3 (Box A-906)
  - Etherington Commission Progress Report, 1972 June 28 (Box A-906)
  - Exim Bank, 1972 June 15 (Box A-906)
  - Farmington Republican Women’s Club, 1973 April 18 (Box A-906)
  - Federal Regional Council, 1972 June 16 (Box A-906)
  - Financial Speech, 1974 (Box A-906)
  - Fiscal Speech, 1973 (Box A-906)
  - Fiscal Responsibility, 1972 January 18 (Box A-906)
  - Fuel Cell (Box A-906)
  - Full Employment, 1972 March 10 (Box A-906)
  - General Assembly Closing, 1972 (Box A-906)
  - General Assembly Opening, 1972 (Box A-906)
  - General Assembly Closing, 1973 June 1 (Box A-906)
  - General Assembly Closing, 1974 May 8 (Box A-906)
  - General Electric, 1971 July 16 (Box A-906)
  - Generation Gap, 1970 June (Box A-906)
  - Gifts to State, 1972 July 14 (Box A-906)
  - Glasphalt, 1972 September 28 (Box A-906)
  - Governing the Government (Box A-906)
  - Guilford (Box A-906)
  - Hartford Hospital: Bliss Wing, 1972 September 15 (Box A-906)
  - Hartford Rotary Club, 1973 April 23 (Box A-906)
  - Hartford Summit Conference, 1973 March 31 (Box A-906)
  - High Flood Pressure, 1973 November 27 (Box A-907)
  - Higher Education, 1973 May 8 (Box A-907)
  - Higher Education National Council, 1973 April 19 (Box A-907)
  - Highways, 1971 November 30 (Box A-907)
  - Highway Openings, 1971 September 23 (Box A-907)
  - Historical Commission, 1972 May 24 (Box A-907)
  - Housing Task Force, 1971 November 12 (Box A-907)
  - Human Services, 1972 September 11 (Box A-907)
  - Inaugural Messages (Box A-907)
  - Independent Union, 1972 October 26 (Box A-907)
  - Industrial Management Club, 1972 October 18 (Box A-907)
  - Institute of Living, 1972 May 22 (Box A-907)
  - Insurance, 1972 March 29 (Box A-907)
  - Interim Message to General Assembly, 1973 January 3 (Box A-907)
  - Jaycee House, 1973 April 26 (Box A-907)
  - Journalistic Society, 1972 April 26 (Box A-907)
  - Knights of Columbus, 1972 March 26 (Box A-907)
  - Land Donation, 1972 December 12 (Box A-907)
  - Landmark Designation, 1972 January (Box A-907)
  - LEAA, 1972 June 9 (Box A-907)
  - Leasing Fraud Conference, 1974 January 21 (Box A-907)
  - Liberation House Dedication (Box A-907)
  - LPN Association, 1972 April 3 (Box A-907)
  - Liquid Gas Plant, 1972 September 29 (Box A-907)
  - Manchester Chamber of Commerce, 1973 September 3 (Box A-907)
  - Manufacturer’s Association, 1972 May 22 (Box A-907)
  - Manufacturing Engineers, 1972 May 10 (Box A-907)
  - Mass Transit, 1973 August 20 (Box A-907)
  - Memorial Day, 1973 May 24 (Box A-907)
  - Mental Health, 1972 May 22 (Box A-907)
  - Mental Retardation, 1972 April 26 (Box A-907)
  - Mental Retardation Office, 1973 May 10 (Box A-907)
  - Mentally Retarded, 1971 December 2 (Box A-907)
  - Meriden Chamber of Commerce, 1973 June 14 (Box A-907)
  - Middlesex Hospital, 1973 September 17 (Box A-907)
  - Middletown Rotary, 1973 September 24 (Box A-907)
  - Milford Academy Graduation, 1973 June 8 (Box A-907)
  - Mohegan Community College, 1972 November 20 (Box A-908)
  - Mount Sinai Hospital, 1972 October 31 (Box A-908)
  - Municipal Chief Executives, 1971 December 15 (Box A-908)
  - NAACP, 1972 September 30 (Box A-908)
  - National Grange, 1972 November 14 (Box A-908)
  - New Britain High School Dedication, 1972 November 19 (Box A-908)
  - New England Association of Fire Chiefs, 1973 June 27 (Box A-908)
  - New England Fuel Institute, 1972 June 19 (Box A-908)
  - New England Energy Crisis Council, 1973 November 15 (Box A-908)
  - New England Police Chiefs’ Association, 1972 September 12 (Box A-908)
  - New Hampshire Primary, 1972 March 3 (Box A-908)
  - New Haven Luncheon Club, 1973 October 1 (Box A-908)
  - New Haven Manufacturers’ Association, 1973 May 7 (Box A-908)
  - New London Chamber of Commerce, 1973 June 17 (Box A-908)
  - New York Reception, 1973 April 6 (Box A-908)
  - Newgate, 1972 May 24 (Box A-908)
  - Noise Abatement, 1972 September 8 (Box A-908)
  - Northern Middlesex Chamber of Commerce, 1973 June 19 (Box A-908)
  - Norwalk Kiwanis Club, 1973 January 11 (Box A-908)
  - Norwich Scott Hill Bridge Ceremony, 1972 October 30 (Box A-908)
  - Norwich Chamber of Commerce, 1973 November 24 (Box A-908)
  - Nurses’ Association, 1971 October 5 (Box A-908)
  - Nurses, 1972 October 26 (Box A-908)
  - Nurses Graduation, 1970 May 23 (Box A-908)
  - Oak Hill School for the Blind, 1971 June 16 (Box A-908)
  - Oil Representative Meeting, 1973 November 29 (Box A-908)
  - Our Lady of the Angels, 1972 June 14 (Box A-908)
  - Parade of Youth Forum, 1972 December 9 (Box A-908)
  - Park Police, 1972 November 27 (Box A-908)
  - Pfizer-Groton Management Clubs, 1973 September 24 (Box A-908)
  - Pharmacists (Box A-908)
  - Pioneer Association, 1971 September 26 (Box A-908)
  - Planning Committee on Criminal Administration, 1972 April 27 (Box A-908)
  - Police, 1972 November 8 (Box A-908)
  - Police Training Program, 1972 November 27 (Box A-908)
  - Political, 1971 September 17 (Box A-908)
  - Prayer Breakfast, 1972 September 21 (Box A-908)
  - Press (Box A-908)
  - Public Employees (Box A-908)
  - PUC Rate Hikes, 1973 June 8 (Box A-908)
  - PUC Remarks, 1973 October 16 (Box A-908)
  - Quinebaug Valley Senior Citizens Center, 1973 May 30 (Box A-908)
  - Railroad Planning, 1974 March 19 (Box A-909)
  - Realtors, 1972 September 13 (Box A-909)
  - Release, 1971 May 19 (Box A-909)
  - Republican State Convention, 1972 June 24 (Box A-909)
  - Revenue Sharing, 1972 September 24 (Box A-909)
  - Revenue Sharing Seminar, 1973 June 14 (Box A-909)
  - Road Builder’s Association, 1971 September 12 (Box A-909)
  - Safety Commission, 1972 September 27 (Box A-909)
  - Safety Messages (Box A-909)
  - St. Francis Hospital, 1972 October 17 (Box A-909)
  - St. Jude’s, 1972 October 17 (Box A-909)
  - Savings Bonds, 1971 December 6 (Box A-909)
  - Senior Citizens Bus Ridership, 1973 May 31 (Box A-909)
  - Services and Expenditures, 1971 March 17 (Box A-909)
  - Sickle Cell (Box A-909)
  - Sigma Delta Chi, 1973 June 14 (Box A-909)
  - Sigma Delta Chi, 1972 June 9 (Box A-909)
  - Sikorsky Aircraft, 1973 May 5 (Box A-909)
  - Soil Conservation, 1972 November 16 (Box A-909)
  - Sons of Italy, New Britain, 1973 May 21 (Box A-909)
  - SE Connecticut Commission on Aging, 1973 May 23 (Box A-909)
  - Southington Apple Festival, 1971 October 9 (Box A-909)
  - Spanish Republican Club, Bridgeport (Box A-909)
  - Spanish Speaking Opportunities Council, 1973 April 18 (Box A-909)
  - Special Olympics, 1973 June 16 (Box A-909)
  - Speeches (Box A-909)
  - Stamford Teachers’ Orientation Day, 1973 September 4 (Box A-909)
  - State and Urban Development, 1974 March 19 (Box A-909)
  - State Central Committee, 1972 February (Box A-909)
  - Statements (Box A-909)
  - State’s Attorney Report on Voter Registration, 1974 January 3 (Box A-909)
  - Steele Testimonial, 1972 September 30 (Box A-909)
  - Submarine Commission (Box A-909)
  - Toll System Investigation (Box A-909)
  - Tourism, 1972 October 5 (Box A-909)
  - Transportation Fund Bill Signing, 1973 June 24 (Box A-910)
  - Tuition (Box A-910)
  - Uncas-on-Thames, 1971 November 3 (Box A-910)
  - UN Day, 1973 November 24 (Box A-910)
  - Union League Club, 1973 November 13 (Box A-910)
  - University of Bridgeport, Tuition (Box A-910)
  - University of Connecticut Student Union Lecture Series, 1973 October 18 (Box A-910)
  - University of New Haven, 1974 January 24 (Box A-910)
  - USS Billfish, 1970 March 12 (Box A-910)
  - Valley Transit District Opening, 1973 January 8 (Box A-910)
  - Vinal Technical School, 1973 May 31 (Box A-910)
  - Vocational Education (Box A-910)
  - Volunteerism, 1972 February 14 (Box A-910)
  - Waterbury Chamber of Commerce, 1973 June 13 (Box A-910)
  - Welfare, 1971 October 19 (Box A-910)
  - West Hartford Chamber of Commerce (Box A-910)
  - West Hartford Republican Convention, 1973 August 22 (Box A-910)
  - Westport Recycling, 1974 April 26 (Box A-910)
  - Winsted GOP, 1973 April 3 (Box A-910)
  - West Virginia, 1972 August 15 (Box A-910)
  - Wiretap Bill, 1971 March 24 (Box A-910)
  - Women, 1972 May 20 (Box A-910)
  - Women, Professional and Business, 1972 September 19 (Box A-910)
  - Yale University, Taft Institute of Government Seminar, 1973 June 29 (Box A-910)
  - YGOP, 1972 March 25 (Box A-910)
  - Young Presidents Organization, 1972 October 18 (Box A-910)
  - Young Republican National Convention, Arizona, 1971 June 23 (Box A-910)
  - Youth, 1971 August 30 (Box A-910)
  - Youth Traffic Safety, 1973 October 26 (Box A-910)
- Series 15. Messages, 1971-1974
  Messages of greetings, congratulations, commemoration, etc.
  - Records (Box A-911)
- Series 16. Public Relations and Communications Files, 1971-1974
  Correspondence, schedules, "shield law" material, etc.
  - Records (Box A-912 - A-914)
- Series 17. Press Releases, 1971-1975
  Releases on Governor's appointments, followed by releases on other subjects.
  Alphabetical.
  - Appointments (Box A-915)
  - Abortion (Box A-916)
  - Administrative Reports (Box A-916)
  - Adoption Laws Advisory (Box A-916)
  - Affirmative Action Plan (Box A-916)
  - Age of Majority (Box A-916)
  - Agriculture Alcoholism (Box A-916)
  - American School for the Deaf (Box A-916)
  - Antelope Hunt (Box A-916)
  - Army (Box A-916)
  - Auditors Reports (Box A-916)
  - Autism (Box A-916)
  - Awards (Box A-916)
  - Banking (Box A-916)
  - Blue Cross (Box A-916)
  - Bluff Point (Box A-916)
  - Boating (Box A-916)
  - Bond Commission (Box A-916)
  - Bradley International Airport (Box A-916)
  - Briefings Budget – Taxes (Box A-916)
  - Budget Crisis (Box A-916)
  - Budget Message, 1973 (Box A-916)
  - Bus Service (Box A-916)
  - Campaign News Releases Census (Box A-916)
  - Cities of the Future, Goldmark (Box A-916)
  - Civil Defense (Box A-916)
  - Child Guidance (Box A-916)
  - Child & Youth Services (Box A-916)
  - Children Treatment Center (Box A-916)
  - Christmas (Box A-916)
  - Christmas Pageant (Box A-916)
  - Claims Commission (Box A-916)
  - Commerce (Box A-916)
  - Commission on Higher Education (Box A-916)
  - Commission on Special Revenue (Box A-916)
  - Commissioners' Reports (Box A-916)
  - Committee of Concern (Box A-916)
  - Community Forums (Box A-917)
  - Condolences (Box A-917)
  - Conn. Development Commission (Box A-917)
  - Conservation & Development Plan (Box A-917)
  - Consumer Affairs (Box A-917)
  - Corrections (Box A-917)
  - Crime (Box A-917)
  - Criminal Administrative Planning Committee (Box A-917)
  - Day Care (Box A-917)
  - Daylight Savings Time (Box A-917)
  - Deficit (Box A-917)
  - Department of Community Affairs (DCA) (Box A-917)
  - Development (Box A-917)
  - Disabilities Disasters (Box A-917)
  - Distinguished Service Award (Box A-917)
  - Downey (Box A-917)
  - Drug Treatment (Box A-917)
  - Drunk Driving (Box A-917)
  - Eastern Office, 2 folders (Box A-918)
  - Economic Advisors (Box A-918)
  - Economic Development Admin. (EDA) (Box A-918)
  - Editorials WFSB - TV 3 (Box A-918)
  - Education (Box A-918)
  - Elderly (Box A-918)
  - Elections (Box A-918)
  - Elections Commission (Box A-918)
  - Electric Boat (Box A-918)
  - Emergency Medical Service (Box A-918)
  - Energy Crisis (Box A-918)
  - Enfield Industrial Project (Box A-918)
  - Environment (Box A-918)
  - Equal Opportunity (Box A-918)
  - Etherington Report (Box A-918)
  - Extradition (2 folders) (Box A-918)
  - Fairfield Hills – Elderly (Box A-918)
  - FCC Application – Ch. 61 (Box A-918)
  - Finance (Box A-918)
  - Fiscal Responsibility (Box A-918)
  - Food (Box A-918)
  - Foreign Affairs (Box A-918)
  - Fuel Conservation (Box A-918)
  - Gasoline Prices (Box A-919)
  - A GING (Box A-919)
  - Golden Eagle Passport (Box A-919)
  - Governors' Conferences (Box A-919)
  - Governors' Portrait (Box A-919)
  - Governor’s Schedule, 1972 November-December (Box A-919)
  - Governor’s Schedule, 1973 January-December (Box A-919)
  - Governor’s Schedule, 1974 January (Box A-919)
  - Governors' Staff (Box A-919)
  - Governors' TV -- Housing (Box A-919)
  - Grasso (Box A-919)
  - Gypsy Moths (Box A-919)
  - Hartford (Box A-920)
  - Hartford Correctional Center (Box A-920)
  - Hartford County Jail (Box A-920)
  - Hartford Day Care (Box A-920)
  - Health (Box A-920)
  - Hearing Impaired (Box A-920)
  - Highway Safety (Box A-920)
  - Highways (Box A-920)
  - Historical Commission (Box A-920)
  - Historical Landmark (Box A-920)
  - Historical Society (Box A-920)
  - Holidays (Box A-920)
  - Honorarium to State Employees (Box A-920)
  - Honorary Membership (Box A-920)
  - Hospital Costs (Box A-920)
  - Housing (Box A-920)
  - HUD (Box A-920)
  - Human Rights and Opportunities (Box A-920)
  - Human Services (Box A-920)
  - International Relations (Box A-920)
  - Information Bureau (Box A-920)
  - Insurance Release Jetport (Box A-920)
  - Judgeships (Box A-920)
  - King, Martin Luther (Box A-920)
  - Labor (Box A-920)
  - Laurel Heights (Box A-920)
  - Law Enforcement Assistance Administration (Box A-920)
  - Lease (Box A-920)
  - Legal Services Legislation, 2 folders (Box A-920)
  - Licensing Fees (Box A-920)
  - Light Metals Coloring Plant (Box A-920)
  - Lobster (Box A-920)
  - Lords Island Lottery (Box A-920)
  - Low Lead Gasoline (Box A-920)
  - Lyndon Baines Johnson (Box A-920)
  - Mager (Box A-921)
  - Mediation and Arbitration Board (Box A-921)
  - Memorial Day (Box A-921)
  - Mental Health (Box A-921)
  - Mental Retardation (Box A-921)
  - Meriden "Pilot Program" (Box A-921)
  - Middletown (Box A-921)
  - Military (Box A-921)
  - Minority Appointments (Box A-921)
  - Mortgages (Box A-921)
  - Motor Vehicle Dept. (Box A-921)
  - Murphy, Francis S. (Box A-921)
  - National Fire Academy (Box A-921)
  - National Youth Science Camp (Box A-921)
  - New England Governors Conference (Box A-921)
  - New England Regional Commission (NERC) (Box A-921)
  - New England River Basin Commission (Box A-921)
  - New Haven (Box A-921)
  - New Haven Community Correction Center (Box A-921)
  - New London Courthouse, 2 folders (Box A-921)
  - Nixon Pardon (Box A-921)
  - Nominations (Box A-921)
  - Norpax (Box A-921)
  - Norwalk Community College (Box A-921)
  - Norwalk Technical School (Box A-921)
  - Norwich (Box A-921)
  - Norwich Hospital (Box A-921)
  - OEO (Box A-921)
  - Official Statements (Box A-921)
  - Oil Drilling (Box A-921)
  - Oil Import (Box A-921)
  - Oil Spills (Box A-921)
  - Olympics (Box A-921)
  - Open Spaces (Box A-921)
  - Pacer (Box A-921)
  - Park Police (Box A-921)
  - Parks and Forests (Box A-921)
  - Personnel Dept. (Box A-921)
  - Petroleum Products Commission (Box A-921)
  - Planning Committee on Criminal Administration (Box A-921)
  - Political Endorsements (Box A-921)
  - Press Advisory – Misc. (Box A-921)
  - Press Conference POW (Box A-921)
  - Proclamation (Box A-921)
  - Prominent Passings (Box A-921)
  - Public Employment Relation Report (Box A-921)
  - Public Expenditure Council (Box A-921)
  - Public Utilities (Box A-921)
  - Public Works (Box A-921)
  - Rail Line (Box A-922)
  - Reapportionment Commission (Box A-922)
  - Recruits (Box A-922)
  - Refineries (Box A-922)
  - Releases Prepared for Other Agencies (Box A-922)
  - Republican National Convention, 1972 (Box A-922)
  - Research Commission (Box A-922)
  - Reservoirs (Box A-922)
  - Resignation (Box A-922)
  - Retirement (Box A-922)
  - Revenue Sharing (Box A-922)
  - Rewards (Box A-922)
  - Rocky Hill Industrial Park (Box A-922)
  - Safety Glass (Box A-922)
  - St. Francis Hospital (Box A-922)
  - Sanitation (Box A-922)
  - Selective Service (Box A-922)
  - Shelton (Box A-922)
  - Small Business Administration (Box A-922)
  - Social Security (Box A-922)
  - Solid Waste (Box A-922)
  - Spanish Speaking (Box A-922)
  - Special Ambassadors (Box A-922)
  - Special Elections (Box A-922)
  - Stamford Branch Office (Box A-922)
  - Stanley Works Fishway (Box A-922)
  - State Ambulance Commission (Box A-922)
  - State Board of Education (Box A-922)
  - state Housing Task Force (Box A-922)
  - State Police (Box A-922)
  - State Song (Box A-922)
  - Summer Employment (Box A-922)
  - Summer Programs (Box A-922)
  - Sunday Blue Laws Surplus, 2 folders (Box A-922)
  - Sympathy (Box A-922)
  - Taxes (Box A-922)
  - Team (Training, Education and Man Power) Grants (Box A-922)
  - Television (Box A-922)
  - Toll Collectors (Box A-922)
  - Traffic (Box A-922)
  - Transportation, 3 folders (Box A-922)
  - Transportation Authority (Box A-922)
  - Treasurer (Box A-922)
  - Truman (Box A-922)
  - Tweed New Haven Airport (Box A-922)
  - Unemployment (Box A-923)
  - U.N. Day (Box A-923)
  - UConn. Library (Box A-923)
  - Valley Transit District (Box A-923)
  - V.D. Task Force Veteran's (Box A-923)
  - Vietnam (Box A-923)
  - Vocational School – Milford (Box A-923)
  - Vocational Technical Schools (Box A-923)
  - Voter Registration (Box A-923)
  - Wage-Price Freeze (Box A-923)
  - Wallingford (Box A-923)
  - Washington Office (Box A-923)
  - Welfare Dept. (Box A-923)
  - Wetlands (Box A-923)
  - Whitney N. Young Jr. (Box A-923)
  - Willimantic (Box A-923)
  - Youth (Box A-923)
- Series 18. Job Requests, Acknowledgements, and Recommendations, 1971-1975
  - Records (Box A-924 - A-925)
- Series 19. Federal Agency Relations File, 1968-1974
  Correspondence with United States Government agencies.
  Alphabetical by subject or name of agency, preceded by unfiled material.
  - Air Force (Box A-926)
  - Army (Box A-926)
  - Census Patronage (Box A-926)
  - Civil Service (Box A-926)
  - Coast Guard (Box A-926)
  - Corrections (Box A-926)
  - Customs (Box A-926)
  - Defense Department (Box A-926)
  - Emigration (Box A-926)
  - Employment (Box A-926)
  - Favor File (Box A-926)
  - FBI (Box A-926)
  - Foreign Service (Box A-926)
  - GSA (Box A-926)
  - GSA (General Services Admn.) (Box A-926)
  - HEW (Box A-926)
  - Immigration (Box A-926)
  - Internal Revenue (Box A-926)
  - Issues (Box A-926)
  - Justice Department (Box A-926)
  - Legislation (Box A-926)
  - Marines (Box A-926)
  - Middle East (Box A-926)
  - Military (Box A-926)
  - Military Academics (Box A-926)
  - Miscellaneous (Box A-926)
  - Naturalization (Box A-926)
  - Navy (Box A-926)
  - Passports (Box A-926)
  - Post Office (Box A-926)
  - POW (Box A-926)
  - Prisons (Box A-926)
  - Social Security (Box A-926)
  - State, 2 folders (Box A-926)
  - State Case Referrals (Box A-926)
  - Technical Assistance (Box A-926)
  - Treasury (Box A-926)
  - U.S. State Department (Box A-926)
  - Veterans (Box A-926)
  - Vietnam (Box A-926)
  - Washington Office (Box A-926)
  - Yellows (Box A-926)
- Series 20. Scrapbook, 1967 January-March
  Mounted newspaper clippings pertaining to Mr. Meskill's first weeks in the U.S. House of Representatives.
  Chronological.
  - Records (Box A-927)
- Series 21. Official Statements, 1971-1975
  Texts of Official Statements by the Governor recognizing or supporting various movements, causes, etc. with related drafts, photographs and correspondence.
  Alphabetical by subject. Folder of denied requests at beginning.
  - Requests for Official Statements not answered in time (Box A-928)
  - Adult Education Month (Box A-928)
  - Aesthetic Environment Year, 1971-1972 (Box A-928)
  - African American History Week (Box A-928)
    See also Negro History Week.
  - Aging: Arts and Crafts Show, May 18-19 (Box A-928)
  - Agriculture USA (TV Message) (Box A-928)
  - Alcoholism Information Month, 1974 May (Box A-928)
  - Alhambra Circus Day (Box A-928)
  - Alien Address Report Month (Box A-928)
  - All-America City (Branford) (Box A-928)
  - All-American Family Week (Box A-928)
  - Altrusa International (Box A-928)
  - Amateur Radio Week (Box A-928)
  - American Business Day (Box A-928)
  - American Business Women’s Association Scholarship Month (Box A-928)
  - American Hungarian Federation Day (Box A-928)
  - American Indian Development Week, 1974 March 18 (Box A-928)
  - American Institute of Banking (Box A-928)
  - American Legion (Message) (Box A-928)
  - American Music Month (Box A-928)
  - America’s Youth on Parade (Baton Twirling) (Message) (Box A-928)
  - Amtrak Month (Box A-928)
  - Ancient Fife & Drum Corps (Deep River) (Box A-928)
  - Ancient Order of Hibernians (Box A-928)
  - Apple Harvest Festival Week (Box A-928)
  - Apple Week (Box A-928)
  - Apprenticeship Week (Box A-928)
  - Aquarium Hobbyist Week (Box A-928)
  - Ararat Lodge, B‘nai B’rith (Box A-928)
  - Armed Forces Week (Box A-928)
  - Armenian Martyrs Day, 1973 April 24 (Box A-928)
  - Army Medical Specialists Corps (Box A-928)
  - Army ROTC Day (Box A-928)
  - Arthritis Foundation Month (Box A-928)
  - Autistic Children’s Week (Box A-928)
  - Automatic Screw Machine Products Week (Box A-928)
  - Awareness Day, 1974 May 1 (Box A-928)
  - Babe Ruth Tournament (Box A-928)
  - Bangladesh Day (Box A-928)
  - Barnum Festival Time (Box A-928)
  - Be Kind to Animals Week (Box A-928)